Someone needs to say something.
The idiot who does the scheduling at the funeral home should be fired.
Liu Min couldn't have done anything.
Why can't they see that?
There's a lot women are better off not knowing.
Now get out.
I need to talk with Mr. Chen.
By the way, Mr. Chen, thank you for what you did for my husband.
I'm sorry it happened.
It's fine, ma'am. We all take and give.
Damn it!
First they investigate Liu Shu.
Then they go after Liu Min.
Someone is gunning for me!
The only positive here is that my worthless son is no longer my problem.
Right, now then.
You get Liu Min's phone?
About that. It's gone.
What? Where is it?
Chen Jin.
You're not a man who makes mistakes, so quit dicking me around.
You wound me, sir.
I'm not interested in your family's secrets, and I can assure you that the police don't have the phone either.
Fine.
You have one more chance.
Get it back to me soon.
My patience only goes so far.
You're a mad genius, boss.
That handoff you set up took me for a loop, but it was the right call.
So since the cops don't have anything on me, when do I get out?
When your holding period is up.
Tell me about the handoff.
How did it go?
That guy in the stairwell.
That was all you, right?
I passed the phone off to them.
Now when I'm caught, I'm clean.
And we leave the cops with nothing.
Just fill me in next time.
I didn't expect anyone.
Especially not there.
Hey!
Oh!
It's just you.
Nearly gave me a heart attack, I swear.
So what's up?
The boss not trust you without a babysitter?
Ha!
Well, I'm telling you right now.
I don't need you here.
Okay.
What's that supposed to mean?
Oh, I see.
Damn, that is good.
Really thinking ahead.
You take care of that now.
Creepy little ninja almost got his neck snapped.
What?